Now we've been through basically the whole dialogue how we can deal with picking somebody up at the
现在我们基本上已经完成了整个对话，我们如何处理在
airport the things we need to say and how to be polite.
机场我们需要说的话以及如何礼貌。
Now the hardest part could be the car ride home.
现在最困难的部分可能是开车回家。
So before we finish this lesson I'd just like to talk about how we can make conversation on the way
所以在我们结束这节课之前，我只想谈谈我们如何在途中进行对话
home if we have a 30 minute car ride.
如果我们有 30 分钟的车程。
We need to have something to talk about and it's a great opportunity for us.
我们需要谈论一些事情，这对我们来说是一个很好的机会。
Me Lydia and David to get to know each other better because before all I've had our emails back and
我让莉迪亚和大卫更好地了解彼此，因为在这之前我已经收到了我们的电子邮件并且
forth with David OK now in the airport we were just talking about essential stuff stuff we need to talk
现在在机场和大卫一起走，我们只是在谈论我们需要谈论的重要事情
about like how their flight was whether or not they need a SIM card or they need to exchange currency
就像他们的航班如何，他们是否需要 SIM 卡或需要兑换货币
or they want to go to their hotel.
或者他们想去他们的旅馆。
That's the basic stuff.
这是基本的东西。
Now we can actually have a conversation.
现在我们可以真正进行对话了。
I don't want to talk too much about this because we really did focus on the important aspects of it
我不想谈论太多，因为我们确实专注于它的重要方面
when we were doing our lesson about asking good questions.
当我们在做关于提出好问题的课程时。
Right.
正确的。
However let's just go through a few things we can say and I want to mention one or two questions which
然而，让我们来看看我们可以说的几件事，我想提一两个问题
are kind of standard but in my opinion not that interesting.
是一种标准，但在我看来不是那么有趣。
So anyway they might ask me questions now I'm sorry Luke.
所以无论如何他们现在可能会问我问题，对不起卢克。
Questions not me.
不是我的问题。
They might ask Luke questions on the car ride home I'm driving.
他们可能会在我开车回家的路上问卢克问题。
Maybe it's 30 minutes or 40 minutes to downtown.
也许到市中心要 30 分钟或 40 分钟。
I don't know why I'm driving like this.
我不知道我为什么要这样开车。
I guess the car is going like this to Mr. insane driver.
我猜这辆车对疯狂的司机先生是这样的。
I don't even have my driver's license.
我连驾照都没有。
OK so they might ask me questions and I can of course talk about New York and I can talk about my job
好的，所以他们可能会问我问题，我当然可以谈论纽约，我可以谈论我的工作
but I can ask them some questions too.
但我也可以问他们一些问题。
So Lydia what plans do you have while you're here in New York.
那么莉迪亚你在纽约的时候有什么计划。
She's not here on business so it's a good opportunity to know what she wants to do.
她不是来这里出差的，所以这是一个了解她想做什么的好机会。
Then we might be able to continue a conversation if she says Oh I'd really like to.
如果她说哦，我真的很想，我们也许可以继续对话。
Blah blah blah blah blah or I don't know then I can recommend something and we can get a conversation
Blah blah blah blah blah 或者我不知道然后我可以推荐一些东西，我们可以进行对话
going or I could ask David a similar question.
或者我可以问大卫一个类似的问题。
I could say David after we finish every day do you have any plans or I could say David besides work.
我可以在我们每天结束后说大卫，你有什么计划，或者我可以说大卫除了工作。
What would you like to do while you're here in New York.
当你在纽约时，你想做什么。
And we can have a conversation about that.
我们可以就此进行对话。
That's a whole conversation that could take the whole 30 minute car ride.
这是一个完整的对话，可能需要整个 30 分钟的车程。
So Lydia what do you do.
所以莉迪亚你是做什么的。
There's a very common question.
有一个很常见的问题。
I know David's job because he's here for business but I don't know what Lydia does.
我知道大卫的工作，因为他是来做生意的，但我不知道莉迪亚是做什么的。
So maybe I can ask this and this means what is your job.
所以也许我可以问这个，这意味着你的工作是什么。
Lydia maybe she says oh I'm just a housewife.
莉迪亚也许她说哦，我只是个家庭主妇。
OK.
好的。
So then we can talk about that or maybe she has a job then we can talk about that.
那么我们可以谈谈那个，或者也许她有工作然后我们可以谈谈那个。
This is just the beginning of a conversation.
这只是对话的开始。
So is this one.
这个也是。
I like this one very much.
我非常喜欢这个。
This is what I will usually ask.
这是我通常会问的问题。
OK.
好的。
You mentioned in your email David that you have two children.
你在电子邮件中提到大卫你有两个孩子。
So are they in school or Now notice I don't really finish the question here.
他们是在学校还是现在注意我并没有真正完成这里的问题。
This is an interesting way to ask a question that we know other people would like to talk about.
这是一种有趣的方式来提出我们知道其他人想谈论的问题。
You know what people love talking about their children.
你知道人们喜欢谈论他们的孩子。
So if you know they have children they will probably go on and on and tell you about their children
所以如果你知道他们有孩子，他们可能会不停地告诉你他们的孩子
for 40 minutes and that's fine.
40分钟，没关系。
That's great.
那太棒了。
So by just saying so are they in school or.
所以只要说他们是在学校还是在学校。
It's like saying I'm giving you permission to start talking about them but you would only use this if
这就像说我允许你开始谈论它们，但你只会在以下情况下使用它
you know that the other person probably has a lot to say if you're not sure then don't use this style
您知道对方可能有很多话要说，如果您不确定，请不要使用这种风格
of sentence can be risky because if you say or.
句子可能有风险，因为如果你说或。
And then they have nothing to say then it can be very awkward OK.
然后他们无话可说，那可能会很尴尬。
So you can use it but only if you know they have a lot to say.
所以你可以使用它，但前提是你知道他们有很多话要说。
I'd love to hear more about your life and your family in London maybe there from from London.
我很想从伦敦那里听到更多关于你在伦敦的生活和家人的信息。
OK this is a similar question but I'm not suggesting that I know anything about their background it
好的，这是一个类似的问题，但我并不是说我对他们的背景一无所知
is more of a statement but it's really a request for information.
更像是一种声明，但它实际上是一种信息请求。
This question in my opinion is a little bit boring.
在我看来，这个问题有点无聊。
I'm not crazy about this one because it's not really focused your life.
我对这个并不疯狂，因为它并没有真正专注于你的生活。
Talk about your life.
谈谈你的生活。
They could really talk about anything.
他们真的可以谈论任何事情。
So on one hand it might be good if there's something they would like to talk about on the other hand
因此，一方面如果他们想谈论一些事情可能会很好
it might not be so good if they don't really know where to begin.
如果他们真的不知道从哪里开始，那可能就不那么好了。
So I could start with this.
所以我可以从这个开始。
Have you ever tried real New York pizza.
你尝过真正的纽约披萨吗？
OK then if they say no then I can recommend some places or if they say yes I can ask them what kind
好的，如果他们说不，那么我可以推荐一些地方，或者如果他们说是，我可以问他们什么样
of pizza they've had.
他们吃过的披萨。
And we can talk about that.
我们可以谈论这个。
I love talking about New York pizza.
我喜欢谈论纽约披萨。
I can talk about that for three hours.
我可以讲三个小时。
So what do you think about New York so far.
那么到目前为止，您对纽约的看法如何。
Now this question you have to be careful about because if we're just driving home sorry to the hotel
现在这个问题你必须小心，因为如果我们只是开车回家对不起酒店
and they have barely been in New York really then they don't really have any impression of New York.
他们几乎没有来过纽约，所以他们对纽约没有任何印象。
So you have to be careful with my want to use this one after maybe they've been here for a day or two.
所以你必须小心我想在他们已经在这里一两天之后使用这个。
Then I meet them for dinner after they've been in New York for a couple of days.
然后在他们在纽约待了几天后，我和他们见面共进晚餐。
And I say So what do you think of New York so far.
我说那么到目前为止，你对纽约的看法如何。
That might be a better question.
这可能是一个更好的问题。
In that situation.
在那种情况下。
OK so David.
好的，大卫。
So David do you follow any sports now.
所以大卫你现在关注任何运动吗？
This question I find to be very boring personally but honestly a lot of people do ask it.
这个问题我个人觉得很无聊，但老实说很多人都会问这个问题。
So I'm including it because it's a common discussion question.
所以我将其包括在内，因为这是一个常见的讨论问题。
It's a common question that comes up in regular conversations.
这是一个经常出现在对话中的常见问题。
When you've met somebody new and you're trying to get to know them you talk about sports maybe talk
当你遇到一个新人并试图了解他们时，你会谈论运动也许会谈论
about movies it's OK but personally I think it's a little boring.
关于电影还可以，但我个人认为这有点无聊。
Now you might have heard.
现在你可能已经听说了。
What about the weather.
天气怎么样。
Right.
正确的。
So we might ask So how's the weather in London this time of year.
所以我们可能会问每年这个时候伦敦的天气怎么样。
How's the weather in England this time of year.
每年这个时候英格兰的天气如何。
You can say it.
你可以说。
People say it.
人们这么说。
Personally I never asked this question because it's so boring.
就我个人而言，我从来没有问过这个问题，因为它太无聊了。
But anyway people do say it.
但无论如何，人们确实会这么说。
So that is how we deal with picking somebody up at the airport going through small talk with them and
这就是我们在机场接人的方式，与他们进行闲聊，然后
handling the essentials the important things we need to handle and having discussions or at least a
处理我们需要处理的重要事情并进行讨论或至少
polite conversation with them on the way back to the hotel on the way downtown.
在回市区的路上和他们礼貌的交谈。
Now that we've been through all of the phrases and things you can say in the picking up someone at the
现在我们已经了解了在接人时可以说的所有短语和事情
airport dialogue I'd like you to practice it.
机场对话我想让你练习一下。
I'd like you to record yourself doing all of the different roles in the dialogue.
我希望你记录下自己在对话中扮演的所有不同角色。
Think about it in this lesson.
在本课中思考它。
I've done all the roles I've recorded it.
我已经完成了所有的 ro我已经记录下来了。
You're watching it right so you can do it by yourself.
你看对了，所以你可以自己做。
I'm.
我是。
I'm doing it by myself.
我自己做。
I'm here in this room right.
我就在这个房间里。
Doing this by myself so you can play all of the roles and imagine that you're picking someone up at
自己做这个，这样你就可以扮演所有的角色，想象你正在接某人
the airport who you've never met before.
你从未见过的机场。
I try to make it interesting.
我试着让它变得有趣。
Tried a couple of times.
试了几次。
Go back listen to the recording see if you can make corrections.
回去听录音，看看能不能改正。
Find mistakes and then try it again.
找出错误，然后再试一次。
Try it again.
再试一遍。
It's a great way to practice.
这是练习的好方法。
All right.
好的。
Good luck and I will see you in the next lesson.
祝你好运，我们下节课见。